anvisoft.com 2018-12-04

# Privacy Policy | Anvisoft

###  **Anvisoft Respects Your Privacy**

As a leading malware fighter expert, Anvisoft collects some personal data from you in order to provide the products and services you request. We will never sell, distribute, or share your personal information, because your trust is the cornerstone of our success. The following Privacy Policy informs you what we collect, how we use and protect your information.

**What Information Do We Collect from You**

Information you give us. For example, many of our services require you to sign up for a Anvisoft Account. When you do, we’ll ask for personal information, like your name, email address, telephone number or credit card. If you want to take full advantage of the sharing features we offer, we might also ask you to create a publicly visible Google Profile, which may include your name and photo.

Information we get from your use of our product. We may collect information about the product that you use and how you use them.

We request your personal information, including your name, address, email address, telephone number.

This happens when you

        ●  Place an order, register a product

        ●  Create a user account

        ●  Join our newsletter

        ●  Send us feedback and make suggestions

        ●  Request a service

        ●  Participate in surveys

**How We Use Your Information**

We use your personal data in the following ways:

        ●  Provide you detailed information about virus alerts, product upgrades, new products, services, newsletter, informative emails, and suggestions about our products improvements

        ●  Provide you with special Anvisoft offers that may be of interest to you

        ●  Assist us in creating better products and services to meet your needs

        ●  Allow you to purchase and download products, obtain access to services, or otherwise engage in activities you select

        ●  Help you quickly find software, services or product information important to you

        ●  Allow you to participate in interactive features of our service, when you chose to do so

        ●  Notify you about changes to our products and service

        ●  We may also use your information to contact you for market research purposes

**Security of Personal Data**

Anvisoft is committed to ensuring that your information is secure. In order to prevent unauthorized access or disclosure, loss, or destruction, and ensure correct use of information, we have put in place suitable physical, technical and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online. At the same time, we strongly advise you not to unveil your password to certain services on our website to anyone.

**Cookies**  

A cookie is a small unique file which is sent by a website to your browser software. Anvisoft may use such cookie to remember you when you visit our site, register for services, or order products. 

You can choose to accept or decline cookies. If you are against this procedure, you can modify your browser settings to reject cookies. However, this may prevent you from using some products and/or services at our website.

**Privacy of Other Companies**

The Anvisoft website may contain links to websites of companies with whom we have a business relationship. Please be aware that these websites have their own Privacy Policy. If you follow a link to anyone of them, we encourage you to read the privacy declaration of these particular companies.

**Non Confidential Information**

Please be aware that the information you submit in a news discussion or forum will be seen as a piece of non-confidential information, such information can be taken and used by others. Therefore, we strongly advise you to carefully control your personal information each time you are online.

**Contact Us**

If you believe that any information we are holding on you is incorrect or incomplete, please contact us, Anvisoft welcomes your comments and suggestions.

Customer Service: support@anvisoft.com
